<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GDS_TourGuideApp</string>
    <string name="category_locations">Locations</string>
    <string name="category_culture">Culture</string>
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>
    <string name="category_sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="int_extra_image">location_details_image</string>
    <string name="int_extra_title">location_details_title</string>
    <string name="int_extra_description">description</string>

    // CultureFragment Content
    <string name="rijksmuseum_title">Rijksmuseum</string>
    <string name="rijksmuseum_description">The Rijksmuseum is a Dutch national museum
        dedicated to arts and history in Amsterdam.</string>
    <string name="van_gogh_title">Van Gogh Museum</string>
    <string name="van_gogh_description">The Van Gogh Museum is an art museum dedicated
        to the works of Vincent van Gogh and his contemporaries in Amsterdam in the
        Netherlands.</string>
    <string name="carre_title">The Royal Theatre Carré</string>
    <string name="carre_description">The Royal Theatre Carré is a Neo-Renaissance theatre
        in Amsterdam, located near the river Amstel.</string>
    <string name="van_loon_title">Museum van Loon</string>
    <string name="van_loon_description">Museum Van Loon is a museum located in a canal-side
        house alongside the Keizersgracht in Amsterdam, Netherlands.</string>
    <string name="maritime_title">Maritime Museum</string>
    <string name="maritime_description">The National Maritime Museum is a maritime museum
        in Amsterdam in the Netherlands. The museum had 419,060 visitors in 2012. It ranked
        as 11th most visited museum in the Netherlands in 2013.</string>

    // FoodFragment Content
    <string name="meatless_district_title">Meatless District</string>
    <string name="meatless_district_description">Bar &amp; Kitchen, 100% vegan, Breakfast,
        Lunch, Dinner &amp; Drinks, Take away, Organic</string>
    <string name="vegan_junk_food_title">Vegan Junk Food</string>
    <string name="vegan_junk_food_description">Cruelty free! Entirely plant-based Vegan Junk
        Food in Amsterdam.</string>
    <string name="vegabond_title">Vegabond Store and Cafe</string>
    <string name="vegabond_description">Vegabond is an intimate lunchroom and vegan grocery
        store in the heart of Amsterdam that sells vegan essentials as well as delicious
        food!</string>
    <string name="mr_mrs_watson_title">Mr &amp; Mrs Watson</string>
    <string name="mr_mrs_watson_description">Awarded Vegan Cheeses. The famous vegan cheeses
        by Mr. &amp; Mrs. Watson are made in-house. Including a cashew brie and blue
        roquefort.</string>
    <string name="terrazen_title">Terrazen Center</string>
    <string name="terrazen_description">Funky, family-run cafe with communal seating offering
        vegan versions of Caribbean &amp; Japanese dishes.</string>
    <string name="las_vegan_title">Las Vegan</string>
    <string name="las_vegan_description">Las Vegan is the world\'s first delivery-only vegan
        restaurant in Amsterdam. 100% plant based vegan food from our kitchen</string>

    // SightsFragment Content
    <string name="anne_frank_title">Anne Frank House</string>
    <string name="anne_frank_description">The Anne Frank House is a writer\'s house and
        biographical museum dedicated to Jewish wartime diarist Anne Frank. The building is
        located on a canal called the Prinsengracht, close to the Westerkerk, in central
        Amsterdam in the Netherlands</string>
    <string name="artis_royal_title">Artis Royal Zoo</string>
    <string name="artis_royal_description">Artis, short for Natura Artis Magistra, is a zoo
        in the centre of Amsterdam. It is the oldest zoo in the Netherlands and one of the
        oldest zoos of mainland Europe</string>
    <string name="rembrandt_title">Rembrandt House</string>
    <string name="rembrandt_description">The Rembrandt House Museum is a historic house and
        art museum in Amsterdam in the Netherlands. Painter Rembrandt lived and worked in the
        house between 1639 and 1656.</string>
    <string name="flower_markets_title">Flower Markets</string>
    <string name="flower_markets_description">The flower market of Amsterdam is a particularly
        colorful place in the city. You will find there all sorts of tulips, narcissus,
        geraniums and many other types of flowers.</string>
    <string name="royal_palace_title">Royal Palace of Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="royal_palace_description">The Royal Palace of Amsterdam in Amsterdam is
        one of three palaces in the Netherlands which are at the disposal of the monarch by
        Act of Parliament.</string>
    <string name="tussauds_title">Madame Tussauds</string>
    <string name="tussauds_description">Madame Tussauds is a wax museum in London with smaller
        museums in a number of other major cities. It was founded bywax sculptor Marie Tussaud.
    </string>
    <string name="poezenboot_title">De Poezenboot</string>
    <string name="poezenboot_description">The Catboat is the only animal sanctuary that
        literally floats. A refuge for stray and abandoned cats which, thanks to its unique
        location on a houseboat in Amsterdam's picturesque canal belt, has also become a
        world-famous tourist attraction. The one and only Catboat.</string>
    <string name="st_nicholas_title">Basilica of St. Nicholas</string>
    <string name="st_nicholas_description">The Basilica of Saint Nicholas is located in the
        Old Centre district of Amsterdam, Netherlands. It is the city's major Catholic
        church.</string>

    // LocationsFragment Content
    <string name="_title"></string>
    <string name="_description"></string>
    <string name="volderpark_title">Volderpark</string>
    <string name="volderpark_description">The Vondelpark is a public urban park of 47 hectares
        (120 acres) in Amsterdam, Netherlands. It is part of the borough of Amsterdam-Zuid and
        situated west from the Leidseplein and the Museumplein. The park was opened in 1865 and
        originally named the \"Nieuwe Park\", but later renamed to \"Vondelpark\", after the
        17th-century playwright and poet Joost van den Vondel. Yearly, the park has around
        10 million visitors. In the park is an open-air theatre, a playground and several
        horeca facilities.</string>
    <string name="westerpark_title">Westerpark</string>
    <string name="westerpark_description">Adjacent to the centre lies the lively Westerpark
        neighbourhood, part of Amsterdam West. Home to the eponymous park, which combines
        expansive greenery with the Westergasfabriek\'s wealth of cultural goings on, this
        lively neighbourhood is home to a varied mix of independent shops, old-school street
        markets, shiny new restaurants and traditional brown cafés.</string>
    <string name="canals_title">The canals</string>
    <string name="canals_description">Alongside wooden clogs, windmills, and tulips, the
        Amsterdam Canals spring to mind when anyone mentions Holland. A canal cruise along the
        Amsterdam Canals is undoubtedly the number one attraction and for first time visitors
        like me, a canal cruise is a great introduction to the city. The Amsterdam Canals also
        celebrate their 400th birthday in 2013 and many special events and festivals are
        helping the city celebrate.</string>
    <string name="jordaan_title">Jordaan District</string>
    <string name="jordaan_description">The Jordaan is a district in the citycenter of
        Amsterdam, known for its beautiful houses, nice restaurants and original shops. When
        in Amsterdam, it is a must to stroll through the little streets and canals. On the
        many bridges over the canals, you can take beautiful pictures and see why Amsterdam is
        called the Venice of the North. Popular streets in the Jordaan are the Prinsengracht,
        the Westerstraat, Haarlemmerstraat and the '9 straatjes' (nine little streets).</string>
    <string name="albert_cuypmarkt_title">Albert Cuypmarkt</string>
    <string name="albert_cuypmarkt_description">The Albert Cuyp Market is a street market in
        Amsterdam, The Netherlands, on the Albert Cuypstraat between Ferdinand Bolstraat and
        Van Woustraat, in the De Pijp area of the Oud-Zuid district of the city.</string>
    <string name="leidseplein_title">Leidseplein</string>
    <string name="leidseplein_description">Leidseplein is a busy square at the southern end
        of Amsterdam\'s central canal ring, almost facing the popular Vondelpark.</string>
    <string name="begijnhof_title">Begijnhof</string>
    <string name="begijnhof_description">The Begijnhof is one of the oldest hofjes in Amsterdam
        , Netherlands. A group of historic buildings, mostly private dwellings, centre on it.
        Today it is also the site of two churches, the Catholic Houten Huys and the English
        Reformed</string>
</resources>
